[Killua] But how?
Stop.
How did you know?
[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in English]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[narrator] At long last,
the time has come.
[heart beating]
[Queen screams]
[all gasp]
-Is it time now?
-Mmm-hmm.
It's the birth of the King.
Wait. It's too early.
[King] Shut up!
Now then, I'm quite famished.
Go and prepare me a feast.
-[Colt] This… this is our King.
-[chorus fades]
[panting]
[Queen gagging]
[gasps]
Your Majesty!
This is terrible.
Her organs have been severely damaged!
[gasps]
[all gasping]
-You.
-[Colt gasps]
Clean it.
[laughs] Would you look at that?
[King] Where is my food?
[Shaiapouf] This way.
[Cheetu] Huh?
We have prepared a meal for you, my King.
Your Highness, the three of us will be
honored to be your devoted servants.
You wish is our command, Your Majesty.
We will fulfill all your earthly desires.
We await your command
with patience, Majesty.
[scoffs]
The Queen needs your assistance now!
We have to stop the bleeding!
Come on. How is she?
[Octopus Ant] It's not good.
She's in bad shape.
If something isn't done…
[grunts angrily]
[Colt] Lord Neferpitou!
The Queen's life is in grave danger.
I only healed him because I need him
for reasons that are my own.
And now that the King has been born,
I'm afraid she just doesn't matter to us.
[gasps]
We don't need that thing anymore.
[Bihorn] Your Majesty.
Tell me,
will Lord Neferpitou grant us their help?
The answer is no, I'm afraid.
The Queen has suffered tremendous damage.
And we simply don't have the power
to heal it.
They may have the power that we need.
Wait, who are you talking about?
Hey, where are you going?
We have already prepared a feast for you
up on the roof, which has a fine view.
[loud crashing]
[Neferpitou] That was excellent.
That looks like fun. [grunts]
[spits]
Disgusting.
[Neferpitou] You don't like it?
I don't. It's horrendously bland.
I'm afraid we don't use
any seasonings, sire.
I would receive the most extremely
luscious nourishment.
Yes, you must be talking about
the ones we call Rares, sire.
More than you could know.
[Neferpitou] As you wish, sire.
In that case…
One of the damn Ants
is heading right for us.
Have we been spotted?
-I say we hide.
-Wait.
Something doesn't quite feel right.
Look at that.
A white flag?
I have come here to surrender.
[both gasp]
She is no longer capable of giving birth.
Wait. What are you saying?
The King has already been born.
-That's impossible.
-It's too soon.
[grunts angrily]
They are all…
evil.
[grunts]
[loud crashing]
[Neferpitou] Might I offer some advice?
[inaudible]
Ah, like this?
Yes, exactly.
I see. It isn't bad.
Still… [spits]
It's not at all worth eating.
Not when you compare it to the Rares.
Might I offer you some more advice?
Do you dare to mock me?
I am aware that one can see the energy
surrounding a body by focusing the eyes.
I hope you can forgive my insolence.
I intended to kill you with that blow.
You have earned my respect.
I am not worthy, sire.
[Bihorn] No. I don't believe it.
[Panda Ant] That's not quite right.
The King, well,
he seems completely different from us.
We're like all other creatures to him.
Nothing more than food.
In that case,
what do you think we should do now?
What are you talking about?
I'm saying that if the Queen dies,
then we really have no reason to stay.
The Queen can't even reproduce anymore.
So what the hell's the point?
[Bihorn gasps]
-That's true, I suppose.
-[Bihorn] Huh?
[Leol] It's no longer possible
for the Queen to maintain her kingdom.
And in that case, I don't see why
we shouldn't all try to become a king.
Something tells me we're not alone.
There are others
who would like to get out of here as well.
[both gasp]
Hey, you guys!
Help us. There isn't much time left.
If the Queen dies,
the squad leaders will be unleashed.
It will be chaos.
What exactly will happen then?
Most likely, they will imitate the King.
They will start spreading their seed,
and building their own kingdoms.
Yes. They're able to mate
with females of other species.
the soldiers will never attempt
to procreate on their own.
But I have read reports of soldiers who,
after the death of their Queen,
Well, Colt,
we're going to take you to our boss
so you two can have a little chat.
Be honest with him,
and tell him everything you just told us.
However, there's no guarantee
he's gonna believe your story.
And even if he does,
well, he may not let you leave,
not alive, anyway.
So are you still willing to come?
Yes, of course. Time is of the essence.
Today's the day our apprentices do battle.
Oh, yeah. I completely forgot.
My money's on Knuckle and Shoot.
And your money, one million of it,
is on all five showing up.
-Hey, Knuckle.
-Yeah?
Just promise me, that you'll save him.
ROOK
I swear on this tile.
[screeching continues]
[Gon] Killua.
I… I never…
[continues crying]
could be so frustrating.
[Killua] Gon…
for the 30 days that you can't use Nen,
I'll protect you.
Whatever it takes, I'll keep you safe.
[closing theme music playing]
[both gasp]
[singer singing in Japanese]